== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)What, why did you get
a party sub?
People are coming over;
it looked fun.
(Sheldon:)Well, we're only watching
Game of Thrones.
(Sheldon:)A party sub implies
it's a party.
(Leonard:)Your attendance implies
it's not.
(Sheldon:)I like a party
as much as the next man,
(Sheldon:)as long as the next man
doesn't like a party.
(Sheldon:)Oh, by the way,
don't forget,
(Sheldon:)tomorrow is our quarterly
Roommate Agreement meeting.
(Leonard:)Oh, Sheldon, we don't
need a meeting
(Leonard:)every three months.
Hmm?
(Sheldon:)Well, it sounds like the kind of
thing one would bring up
(Sheldon:)at a quarterly
Roommate Agreement meeting.
(Sheldon:)Lucky for you it's tomorrow.
(Leonard:)Oh, you know what?
(Leonard:)I'm not going.
(Sheldon:)Well, you have to go.
(Sheldon:)It's Penny's first time leading
the Pledge of Allegiance.
(Leonard:)This meeting is a waste of time.
(Leonard:)Whether we make the switch
(Leonard:)from Post Raisin Bran
to Kellogg's Raisin Bran
(Leonard:)should not require
parliamentary procedure.
(Sheldon:)You realize one of them
has sugar on the raisins.
(Leonard:)You're the only one
who eats them!